[ar: Bon Jovi]
[ti: Always]
[al: Cross Road: The Best of Bon Jovi]
[by: ferryman4u]
[length: 05:52]
[id: kwkuzhcc]

[00:00.54]Yeah, i will love you baby - always
[00:14.17]And i'll be there forever and a day - always
[00:27.91]If you told me to cry for you
[00:33.47]I could
[00:35.26]If you told me to die for you
[00:40.41]I would
[00:41.97]Take a look at my face
[00:44.96]There's no price i won't pay
[00:50.36]To say these words to you
[00:59.45]
[01:21.34]Well, there ain't no luck
[01:23.02]In these loaded dice
[01:24.32]But baby if you give me just one more try
[01:27.50]We can pack up our old dreams
[01:29.24]And our old lives
[01:30.85]We'll find a place where the sun still shines
[01:34.51]And i will love you, baby - always
[01:46.97]And i'll be there forever and a day - always
